8020japanese.com 2019-05-22

# Privacy Policy - 80/20 Japanese

We care a great deal about our customers’ privacy and the trust that you put in us when sharing your personal information. This Privacy Policy outlines our practices on data collection so that you are confident your personal information is secure and free from abuse and misuse. By visiting 8020japanese.com, you accept and consent to the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

### Information Collection

The information collected from you will be used for the purpose of processing your purchase orders and managing our relationship with you.

We may use your personal information to send you marketing and/or promotional materials from time to time. You can unsubscribe from marketing information at anytime by using the unsubscribe function within the electronic marketing material, or via [this link](https://8020japanese.us8.list-manage.com/unsubscribe?u=36e9b05a3afff8336ad6fd26d&id=6e98f99a67).

We will never sell your personal information to any third parties. We do, however, have certain Third Party Service Providers who perform important business functions on our behalf. These include processing payments, fulfilling orders and delivering packages. They have access to personal data needed to carry out their functions, but they may not use it for other purposes. We require that all our Third Party Service Providers process personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

You have the right to request access to and the correction of information about you held by us. If you wish to access or correct your personal data held by us, please [contact us](http://8020japanese.com/contact/).

### Security of Your Personal Information

Financial transactions are handled by third party service providers (PayPal & Stripe) who protect the security of your transaction information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. We do not store or have access to your financial or credit card information.

For other personal information provided to us by you, such as your name, email address, and mailing address, we ensure that this information is safely and securely stored. We protect your personal information by using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology for the transmission of your personal information, storing it on secure servers, and restricting access to this information.

### Collection of Computer Data

When you visit 80/20 Japanese, our servers will automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. This data may include:

– Your computer’s IP address  
– Browser type  
– Webpage you were visiting before you came to our site  
– The pages within 80/20 Japanese that you visit  
– The time spent on those pages, items and information searched for on our site, access times and dates, and other statistics.

This information is collected for analysis and evaluation in order to help us improve our site and the services and products we provide. This data will not be used in association with any other personal information.

### Cookie Use for Remarketing

We may use Google Analytics, Google AdWords and/or Facebook remarketing services to advertise on third party websites to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, such as making a purchase or using the contact form to make an enquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, a site in the Google Display Network or DoubleClick advertising network, or somewhere on Facebook. Third-party vendors, including Google & Facebook, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the 80/20 Japanese website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy, as well as Google & Facebook privacy policies.

You can opt-out of remarketing by visiting the links below:

For Google, click [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) and/or [here](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en).

For Facebook, click [here](https://www.facebook.com/ads/website_custom_audiences/).

### Changes To Our Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy without providing you with advance notice of our intent to make these changes.

### Questions?

If you have any queries about our Privacy Policy and practices, please [contact us](http://8020japanese.com/contact/).
